Guide to the Ted Fagan Collection
Stanford Archive of Recorded Sound
- Reel to reel tapes
  - Wiener Festwochen. Wagner, Richard, 1813-1883. Rienzi. Part II 1960, 10" reel (Box 26, Folder 682)
    (Fagan's original numbering XL) Svanholm, Set as Cola Rienzi; Christiansen, Asger Lund as Irene; Schoeffler, Paul as Steffano Colonna; Ludwig, Christa as Adriano; Berry, Walter as Paolo Orsini; Holecek, Heinz as Raimondo; Terkal, Karl, 1919- as Baroncelli; Pernerstorfer, Alois, 1912-1978 as Cecco del Vecchio; Stich-Randall, Teresa, 1927- as Messaggiero di Pace. Singverein der Musikfreunde. Wiener Sängerknaben and Wiener Philharmoniker. Krips, Joseph, conductor
  - Wiener Festwochen. Wagner, Richard, 1813-1883. Rienzi. Part III 1960, 10" reel (Box 26, Folder 683)
    (Fagan's original numbering XLI) Svanholm, Set as Cola Rienzi; Christiansen, Asger Lund as Irene; Schoeffler, Paul as Steffano Colonna; Ludwig, Christa as Adriano; Berry, Walter as Paolo Orsini; Holecek, Heinz as Raimondo; Terkal, Karl, 1919- as Baroncelli; Pernerstorfer, Alois, 1912-1978 as Cecco del Vecchio; Stich-Randall, Teresa, 1927- as Messaggiero di Pace. Singverein der Musikfreunde. Wiener Sängerknaben and Wiener Philharmoniker. Krips, Joseph, conductor
  - Wiener Festwochen. Mahler, Gustav, 1860-1911. Symphony, no. 4, G major.1960, 10" reel (Box 26, Folder 684)
    (Fagan's original numbering XLII) Schwarzkopf, Elisabeth, soprano. Wiener Philharmoniker. Walter, Bruno, 1876-1962, conductor
  - Salzburger Festspiele. Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901. Messa da Requiem 1962, 10" reel (Box 26, Folder 685)
    (Fagan's original numbering XLII) Price, Leontyne, soprano; Simionatto, Giuletta, alto; Zampieri, Giuseppe, 1921-1981, tenor; Ghiaurov, Nicolai, 1929-2004, bass. Berliner Philharmoniker. Singverein der Musikfreunde, Wien. Karajan, Herbert von, conductor
  - Cherubini, Luigi, 1760-1842. Eliza, 10" reel (Box 26, Folder 686)
    (Fagan's original numbering XLIV) Tucci, Gabriella, soprano. Maggio musicale fiorentino. Orchestra. Capuana, Franco, conductor
  - Garden, Mary, 1874-1967, soprano, 10" reel (Box 26, Folder 687)
    (Fagan's original numbering XLV. Taped from discs)
  - Lehmann, Lotte Master Class at Wigmore Hall, London, 10" reel (Box 26, Folder 688)
    (Fagan's original numbering XLVI) Singers: Godfrey, Victor, 1934; Allen, Josephine; Bumbry, Grace, 1937-. Newton,Ivor, piano
  - Instrumental, 10" reel (Box 26, Folder 689)
    (Fagan's original numbering XLVII. Taped from discs)
  - Wiener Festwochen. Berg, Alban, 1885-1935. Lulu 1960, 10" reel (Box 26, Folder 690)
    (Fagan's original numbering XLVIII) Lear, Evelyn as Lulu; Kobeck-Peters, Margit as Countess Geschwitz; Sjöstedt, Margarete as a theatrical dresser/a High-School boy/a groom; Equiluz, Kurt as a painter; Rehfuss, Heinz as Dr. Schön; Munteanu, Petre, 1919- as Alwa; Colombo, Scipio as an animal tamer/an athlete; Braun, Hans as the doctor/Schigolch/theater director; Majkut, Erich as the prince/butler. Wiener Philharmoniker. Maderna, Bruno, conductor
  - Donizetti, Gaetano, 1797-1848. Elisir d'amore. Broadcast Texaco-Metropolitan Opera Radio Network Dec. 24, 1960, 10" reel (Box 26, Folder 691)
    (Fagan's original numbering IL) Formichini, Dino as Nemorino; Söderström, Elisabeth, 1927- as Adina; Guarrera, Frank, 1923- as Sergeant Belcore; Corena, Fernando as Dr. Dulcamara. Metropolitan Opera Orchestra. Cleva, Fausto, conductor
  - United Nations Day Concert. Part I1960, 10" reel (Box 26, Folder 692)
    (Fagan's original numbering L) Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Suites, orchestra, BWV 1068, D major. Orchestre de la Suisse Romande. Ansermet, Ernest, 1883-1969, conductor -- Fischer-Dieskau, Dietrich, 1925-, baritone. Wolf, Hugo, 1860-1903. Goethe-Lieder. Harfenspieler. Japanese Symphony Orchestra. Kletzki, Paul, conductor -- Remarks by UN Secretary General, Hammarskjöld, Dag, 1905-1961 -- Davy, Gloria, soprano; Nikolaidi, Elena, 1909-, mezzo-soprano; Vickers, Jon, tenor; Sze, Yi-Kwei, 1915-1994, bass. Beethoven, Ludwig van, 1770-1827. Symphonies, no. 9, op. 125, D minor. Philadelphia Symphony Orchestra. Temple Univesity Chorus. Ormandy, Eugene, 1899-1985, conductor
  - United Nations Day Concert. Part II1960, 10" reel (Box 26, Folder 693)
    (Fagan's original numbering LI) Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Suites, orchestra, BWV 1068, D major. Orchestre de la Suisse Romande. Ansermet, Ernest, 1883-1969, conductor -- Fischer-Dieskau, Dietrich, 1925-, baritone. Wolf, Hugo, 1860-1903. Goethe-Lieder. Harfenspieler. Japanese Symphony Orchestra. Kletzki, Paul, conductor -- Remarks by UN Secretary General, Hammarskjöld, Dag, 1905-1961 -- Davy, Gloria, soprano; Nikolaidi, Elena, 1909-, mezzo-soprano; Vickers, Jon, tenor; Sze, Yi-Kwei, 1915-1994, bass. Beethoven, Ludwig van, 1770-1827. Symphonies, no. 9, op. 125, D minor. Philadelphia Symphony Orchestra. Temple Univesity Chorus. Ormandy, Eugene, 1899-1985, conductor
  - Historic performances of Wagner, Richard, 1813-1883, 10" reel (Box 26, Folder 694)
    (Fagan's original numbering LII. Taped from discs)
  - Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901. Nabucco. Broadcast Texaco-Metropolitan Opera Radio Network Dec. 3, 1960, 10" reel (Box 26, Folder 695)
    (Fagan's original numbering LIII) Siepi, Cesare as Zaccaria; Fernandi, Eugenio as Isamele; Elias, Rosalind as Fenena; Rysanek, Leonie as Abigaille; Ordassy, Carlotta as Anna; MacNeil, Cornell, 1922- as Nabucco; Giaiotti, Bonaldo as high priest of Baal; Franke, Paul, 1920- as Abdallo. Metropolitan Opera Orchestra. Schippers, Thomas, conductor
  - Bachwoche Ansbach. Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Masses, BWV 232, B minor 1961, 10" reel (Box 26, Folder 696)
    (Fagan's original numbering LIV) Buckel, Ursula, soprano; Töpper, Hertha, alto; Häfliger, Ernst, tenor; Engen, Kieth, bass. Münchener Bach-Chor. Richter, Karl, 1926-1981, conductor
  - Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901. Rigoletto. Broadcast Texaco-Metropolitan Opera Radio Network Dec. 31, 1960, 10" reel (Box 27, Folder 697)
    (Fagan's original numbering LV) Morell, Barry as the Duke; Carelli, Gabor as Borsa; Stratas, Teresa as Countess Ceprano; Cehanovsky, George, 1892-1986 as Count Ceprano; MacNeil, Cornell, 1922- as Rigoletto; Harvuot, Clifford, 1912- as Marullo; Giaiotti, Bonaldo as Monterone; Tozzi, Giorgio as Sparafucile; Peters, Roberta, 1930- as Gilda; Votipka, Thelma as Giovanna; Wall, Joan as a page; de Paola, Paul as the chief guard; Dunn, Mignon as Maddalena. Metropolitan Opera Orchestra. Verchi, Nino, conductor
  - Mussorgsky, Modest Petrovich, 1839-1881. Boris Godunov (1869). Broadcast Texaco-Metropolitan Opera Radio Network. Part I, 10" reel (Box 27, Folder 698)
    (Fagan's original numbering LVI) Sgarro, Louis, 1920-1985 as Nikitich; Powell, Thomas as Mityukh; Votipka, Thelma as a peasant woman; Marsh, Calvin as Shchelkalov; Kelley, Norman as Prince Vassili Ivanovich Shuiski; London, George, 1920-1985 as Boris Godunov; Tozzi, Giorgio as brother Pimen; Sullivan, Brian as Grigori; Lipton, Martha as the innkeeper; Anthony, Charles, 1929- as Missail; Alvary, Lorenzo, 1909- as Varlaam; Hawkins, Osie as an officer of the frontier guard; Stratas, Teresa as Xenia; Vanni, Helen as Fyodor; Dunn, Mignon as Xenia's nurse; Nagy, Robert, 1929- as a Boyar; Thebom, Blanche as Marina Mnishek; Borg, Kim as Rangoni; Franke, Paul, 1920- as a simpleton; Balestrieri, Antonio as Khrushchov; Trehy, John as Lavitski; Roberts, Hal as Chernikovski. Metropolitan Opera Orchestra. Leinsdorf, Erich, 1912-1993, conductor
  - Mussorgsky, Modest Petrovich, 1839-1881. Boris Godunov (1869). Broadcast Texaco-Metropolitan Opera Radio Network. Part II, 10" reel (Box 27, Folder 699)
    (Fagan's original numbering LVII) Sgarro, Louis, 1920-1985 as Nikitich; Powell, Thomas as Mityukh; Votipka, Thelma as a peasant woman; Marsh, Calvin as Shchelkalov; Kelley, Norman as Prince Vassili Ivanovich Shuiski; London, George, 1920-1985 as Boris Godunov; Tozzi, Giorgio as brother Pimen; Sullivan, Brian as Grigori; Lipton, Martha as the innkeeper; Anthony, Charles, 1929- as Missail; Alvary, Lorenzo, 1909- as Varlaam; Hawkins, Osie as an officer of the frontier guard; Stratas, Teresa as Xenia; Vanni, Helen as Fyodor; Dunn, Mignon as Xenia's nurse; Nagy, Robert, 1929- as a Boyar; Thebom, Blanche as Marina Mnishek; Borg, Kim as Rangoni; Franke, Paul, 1920- as a simpleton; Balestrieri, Antonio as Khrushchov; Trehy, John as Lavitski; Roberts, Hal as Chernikovski. Metropolitan Opera Orchestra. Leinsdorf, Erich, 1912-1993, conductor
  - Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791. Nozze di Figaro. Broadcast Texaco-Metropolitan Opera Radio Network. Part I Jan. 28, 1961, 10" reel (Box 27, Folder 700)
    (Fagan's original numbering LVIII) Siepi, Cesare as Figaro; Peters, Roberta as Susanna; Flagello, Ezio as Dr. Bartolo; Resnik, Regina, 1922- as Marcellina; Miller, Mildred as Cherubino; Borg, Kim as Count Almaviva; Carelli, Gabor as Basilio; Amara, Lucine as Countess Rosina Almaviva; Alvary, Lorenzo, 1909- as Antonio; Nagy, Robert, 1929- as Don Curzio; Allen, Mildred as Barbarina; Peasant girls: Clark, Charlene; Shawn, Dorothy. Metropolitan Opera Orchestra. Leinsdorf, Erich, 1912-1993, conductor
  - Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791. Nozze di Figaro. Broadcast Texaco-Metropolitan Opera Radio Network. Part IIJan. 28, 1961, 10" reel (Box 27, Folder 701)
    (Fagan's original numbering LIX) Siepi, Cesare as Figaro; Peters, Roberta as Susanna; Flagello, Ezio as Dr. Bartolo; Resnik, Regina, 1922- as Marcellina; Miller, Mildred as Cherubino; Borg, Kim as Count Almaviva; Carelli, Gabor as Basilio; Amara, Lucine as Countess Rosina Almaviva; Alvary, Lorenzo, 1909- as Antonio; Nagy, Robert, 1929- as Don Curzio; Allen, Mildred as Barbarina; Peasant girls: Clark, Charlene; Shawn, Dorothy. Metropolitan Opera Orchestra. Leinsdorf, Erich, 1912-1993, conductor
  - Strauss, Richard, 1864-1949. Arabella. Broadcast Texaco-Metropolitan Opera Radio Network. Jan. 21, 1961, 10" reel (Box 27, Folder 702)
    (Fagan's original numbering LX) Votipka, Thelma as a fortuneteller; Dunn, Mignon as Countess Adelaide von Waldner; Rothenberger, Anneliese as Zdenka; Morell, Barry as Matteo; Della Casa, Lisa as Arabella; Nagy, Robert, 1929- as Count Elemer; Herbert, Ralph as Count Theodor von Waldner; Mayreder, Rudolf as a waiter; London, George, 1920-1985 as Mandryka; Folmer, Joseph as Welko; Reitan, Roald as Count Dominik; Scott, Norman as Count Lamoral; Hurley, Laurel as the Fiakermilli; Kuestner, Charles as Djura; Birlenbach, Erich as Jankel. Metropolitan Opera Orchestra. Leinsdorf, Erich, 1912-1993, conductor
  - Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901. Simon Boccanegra Feb. 18, 1961, 10" reel (Box 27, Folder 703)
    (Fagan's original numbering LXI) Flagello, Ezio as Paolo Albiani; Scott, Norman, 1921-1968 as Pietro; Colzani, Anselmo as Simon Bocanegra; Tozzi, Giorgio as Jacopo Fiesco; Tebaldi, Renata as Amelia Grimaldi; Tucker, Richard, 1913-1975 as Gabriele Adorno; Vicos, Thena as a maidservant. Metropolitan Opera Orchestra.
  - Flagstad, Kirsten, 1895-1962. Part II, 10" reel (Box 27, Folder 704)
    (Fagan's original numbering LXII. Taped from discs)
  - Flagstad, Kirsten, 1895-1962. Part III, 10" reel (Box 27, Folder 705)
    (Fagan's original numbering LXIII. Taped from discs)
  - Interview with Buxton, Sonny of KGO. July 18, 1976, 10" reel (Box 27, Folder 706)
    (Fagan's original numbering LXIV) Taped from a telephone conversation.
  - Busoni, Ferruccio, 1866-1924. Doktor Faust, 10" reel (Box 27, Folder 707)
    (Fagan's original numbering LXV) Wallace, Ian as Wagner; Fischer-Dieskau, Dietrich, 1925- as Faust; Lervi, Rd [?] as Mephisto; Cameron, John as the Duke of Parma; Harper, Heather as the Duchess of Parma. London Symphony Orchestra. Boult, Adrian, 1889-1983, conductor
  - Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901. Trovatore. Broadcast Texaco-Metropolitan Opera Radio Network. Feb. 4, 1961, 10" reel (Box 27, Folder 708)
    (Fagan's original numbering LXVI) Wildermann, William, 1919-2004 as Ferrando; Vanni, Helen as Inez; Price, Leontyne as Leonora; Merrill, Robert, 1917-2004 as Count die Luna; Corelli, Franco as Manrico; Dalis, Irene as Azucena; Tomanelli, Carlo as a gypsy; Nagy, Robert, 1929- as a messenger; Anthony, Charles, 1929- as Ruiz. Metropolitan Opera Orchestra. Cleva, Fausto, conductor
  - 10" reel (Box 27, Folder 709)
    (Fagan's original numbering LXVII. Tape and card missing)
  - Ponchielli, Amilcare, 1834-1886. Gioconda April 1, 1961, 10" reel (Box 27, Folder 710)
    (Fagan's original numbering LXVIII) Merrill, Robert, 1917-2004 as Barnaba; Milanov, Zinka as La Gioconda; Dunn, Mignon as La Cieca; Cehanovsky, George, 1892-1986 as Zuane; De Paolis, Alessio as Isepo; Baum, Kurt, 1900-1989 as Enzo Grimaldo; Rankin, Nell as Laura Adorno; Wildermann, William, 1919-2004 as Alvise Badoero; Sgarro, Louis, 1920-1985 as a monk; Barbusci, Nicola as a streetman; Two street singers: De Paola, Paul; Balestrieri, Antonio. Metropolitan Opera Orchestra. Cleva, Fausto, conductor
  - Berlioz, Hector, 1803-1869. Damnation de Faust. Part I, 10" reel (Box 27, Folder 711)
    (Fagan's original numbering LXIX. Part II in Tape 362) Poleri, David as Faust; Singher, Martial as Mephistopheles; Danco, Suzanne as Marguerite; Gramm, Donald as Brander. Boston Symphony Orchestra. Harvard-Ratcliff Chorus. Munch, Charles, 1891-1968, conductor
  - Handel, George Frideric, 1685-1759. Acis and Galatea, 10" reel (Box 27, Folder 712)
    (Fagan's original numbering LXX. Taped from discs)
  - Strauss, Richard, 1864-1949. Ariadne auf Naxos, 10" reel (Box 27, Folder 713)
    (Fagan's original numbering LXXI. Taped from discs)
  - Mahler, Gustav, 1860-1911. Symphonies, no. 1, D major, 10" reel (Box 27, Folder 714)
    (Fagan's original numbering LXXII. Taped from discs)
  - Orff, Carl, 1895-1982. Mond; Kluge, 10" reel (Box 28, Folder 715)
    (Fagan's original numbering LXXIII. Taped from discs)
  - Menotti, Gian Carlo, 1911-2007. Saint of Bleecker Street, 10" reel (Box 28, Folder 716)
    (Fagan's original numbering LXXIV) Xavier Symphony Society. La Selva, Vincent, conductor
  - Berg, Alban, 1885-1935. Wozzeck. Broadcast Texaco-Metropolitan Opera Radio Network. April 8, 1961, 10" reel (Box 28, Folder 717)
    (Fagan's original numbering LXXV) Franke, Paul, 1920- as the captain; Uhde, Hermann, 1914-1965 as Franz Wozzeck; Anthony, Charles, 1929- as Andres; Steber, Eleanor as Marie; Roggero, Margaret as Margret; Baum, Kurt, 1921-2000 as Drum major; Cooke, Thomas as Marie's child; Herbert, Ralph as the doctor; Flagello, Ezio as first apprentice; Marsh, Calvin as second apprentice; De Paolis, Alessio as the fool; Ringland, Earl as a soldier; Kuestner, Charles as a townsman. Metropolitan Opera Orchestra. Boehm, Karl, conductor
  - Donizetti, Gaetano, 1797-1848. Rita, 10" reel (Box 28, Folder 718)
    (Fagan's original numbering LXXVI)
  - Rossini, Gioacchino, 1792-1868. Cambiale di matrimonio, 10" reel (Box 28, Folder 719)
    (Fagan's original numbering LXXVII)
  - Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791. Don Giovanni, 10" reel (Box 28, Folder 720)
    (Fagan's original numbering LXXVIII. Taped from discs)
  - Piano concerti - Romantic, 10" reel (Box 28, Folder 721)
    (Fagan's original numbering LXXIX. Taped from discs)
  - Piano - Various - Romantic, 10" reel (Box 28, Folder 722)
    (Fagan's original numbering LXXX. Taped from discs)
  - Bayreuther Festspiele. Wagner, Richard, 1813-1883. Lohengrin. Part I 1960, 10" reel (Box 28, Folder 723)
    (Fagan's original numbering LXXXI) Adam, Theo as King Henry the Fowler; Windgassen, Wolfgang as Lohengrin; Løvberg, Aase Nordmo, 1923- as Elsa; Neidlinger, Gustav, 1910-1991 as Telramund; Varnay, Astrid as Ortrud; Wächter, Eberhard as King's Herald; Krug, Wilfried as first nobleman; Winkler, Hermann as second nobleman; Nöcker, Hans Günter, 1927- as third nobleman; Janowitz, Gundula as first noblewoman; Witzmann, Elisabeth as second noblewoman; Schoenemann, Hildegard as third noblewoman; Hellmann, Claudia as fourth noblewoman. Bayreuther Festspiele Orchester. Maazel, Lorin, 1930-, conductor
  - Bayreuther Festspiele. Wagner, Richard, 1813-1883. Lohengrin. Part II 1960, 10" reel (Box 28, Folder 724)
    (Fagan's original numbering LXXXII) Adam, Theo as King Henry the Fowler; Windgassen, Wolfgang as Lohengrin; Løvberg, Aase Nordmo, 1923- as Elsa; Neidlinger, Gustav, 1910-1991 as Telramund; Varnay, Astrid as Ortrud; Wächter, Eberhard as King's Herald; Krug, Wilfried as first nobleman; Winkler, Hermann as second nobleman; Nöcker, Hans Günter, 1927- as third nobleman; Janowitz, Gundula as first noblewoman; Witzmann, Elisabeth as second noblewoman; Schoenemann, Hildegard as third noblewoman; Hellmann, Claudia as fourth noblewoman. Bayreuther Festspiele Orchester. Maazel, Lorin, 1930-, conductor
  - Bayreuther Festspiele. Wagner, Richard, 1813-1883. Lohengrin. Part III 1960, 10" reel (Box 28, Folder 725)
    (Fagan's original numbering LXXXIII) Adam, Theo as King Henry the Fowler; Windgassen, Wolfgang as Lohengrin; Løvberg, Aase Nordmo, 1923- as Elsa; Neidlinger, Gustav, 1910-1991 as Telramund; Varnay, Astrid as Ortrud; Wächter, Eberhard as King's Herald; Krug, Wilfried as first nobleman; Winkler, Hermann as second nobleman; Nöcker, Hans Günter, 1927- as third nobleman; Janowitz, Gundula as first noblewoman; Witzmann, Elisabeth as second noblewoman; Schoenemann, Hildegard as third noblewoman; Hellmann, Claudia as fourth noblewoman. Bayreuther Festspiele Orchester. Maazel, Lorin, 1930-, conductor
  - Farrell, Eileen, 1920-2002 1960, 10" reel (Box 28, Folder 726)
    (Fagan's original numbering LXXXIV. Taped from discs)
  - Paino - Various - Romantic, 10" reel (Box 28, Folder 727)
    (Fagan's original numbering LXXXV. Taped from discs)
  - Paino - Various - Romantic, 10" reel (Box 28, Folder 728)
    (Fagan's original numbering LXXXVI. Taped from discs)
  - Bayreuther Festspiele. Wagner, Richard, 1813-1883. Parsifal. Act I 1960, 10" reel (Box 28, Folder 729)
    (Fagan's original numbering LXXXVII. ) Bayreuther Festspiele Orchester.
  - Bayreuther Festspiele. Wagner, Richard, 1813-1883. Parsifal. Act II 1960, 10" reel (Box 28, Folder 730)
    (Fagan's original numbering LXXXVIII. ) Bayreuther Festspiele Orchester.
  - Bayreuther Festspiele. Wagner, Richard, 1813-1883. Parsifal. Act III 1960, 10" reel (Box 28, Folder 731)
    (Fagan's original numbering LXXXIX. ) Bayreuther Festspiele Orchester.
  - Bayreuther Festspiele. Wagner, Richard, 1813-1883. Wagner, Richard, 1813-1883. Meistersinger von Nürnberg. Part I 1960, 10" reel (Box 28, Folder 732)
    (Fagan's original numbering XC) Greindl, Josef as Hans Sachs; Adam, Theo as Veit Pgner; Krug, Wilfried as Kunz Vogelgesang; Koch, Egmont, 1906-1966 as Konrad Nachtigal; Schmitt-Walter, Karl, 1900-1985 as Sixtus Beckmesser; Weber, Ludwig as Fritz Kothner; Zimmermann, Heinz-Günther as Balthasar Zorn; Neukirch, Harald as Ulrich Eisslinger; Winkler, Hermann as Augustin Moser; Sentpaul, Frithjof as Hermann Ortel; Nöcker, Hans Günter, 1927- as Hans Schwarz; Windgassen, Wolfgang as Walther von Stolzing; Stoltz, Gerhard as David; Grümmer, Elisabeth as Eva; Schärtel, Elisabeth as Magdalene; Bell, Donald as a nightwatchman. Bayreuther Festspiele Orchester. Knappertsbusch, Hans, 1888-1965, conductor
  - Bayreuther Festspiele. Wagner, Richard, 1813-1883. Wagner, Richard, 1813-1883. Meistersinger von Nürnberg. Part II 1960, 10" reel (Box 29, Folder 733)
    (Fagan's original numbering XCI) Greindl, Josef as Hans Sachs; Adam, Theo as Veit Pgner; Krug, Wilfried as Kunz Vogelgesang; Koch, Egmont, 1906-1966 as Konrad Nachtigal; Schmitt-Walter, Karl, 1900-1985 as Sixtus Beckmesser; Weber, Ludwig as Fritz Kothner; Zimmermann, Heinz-Günther as Balthasar Zorn; Neukirch, Harald as Ulrich Eisslinger; Winkler, Hermann as Augustin Moser; Sentpaul, Frithjof as Hermann Ortel; Nöcker, Hans Günter, 1927- as Hans Schwarz; Windgassen, Wolfgang as Walther von Stolzing; Stoltz, Gerhard as David; Grümmer, Elisabeth as Eva; Schärtel, Elisabeth as Magdalene; Bell, Donald as a nightwatchman. Bayreuther Festspiele Orchester. Knappertsbusch, Hans, 1888-1965, conductor
  - Friars Club (New York, N.Y.) Reception and testimonial dinner for Bogart, Humphrey, 1899-1957. 1955, 10" reel (Box 29, Folder 734)
    (Fagan's original numbering XCII)
  - Donizetti, Gaetano, 1797-1848. Lucia di Lammermoor 1958, 10" reel (Box 29, Folder 735)
    (Fagan's original numbering XCIII) Callas, Maria, 1923-1977, soprano; Fernandi, Eugenio, tenor; Panerai, Rolando, baritone; Formichini, Dino, tenor; Modesti, Giuseppe, bass. Radiotelevisione italiana. Orchestra sinfonica di Milano. Serafin, Tullio, 1878-1968, conductor
  - Price, Leontyne, soprano, 10" reel (Box 29, Folder 736)
    (Fagan's original numbering XCIV) Strauss, Richard, 1864-1949. Lieder, op. 19. Wie sollten wir geheim sie halten; Lieder, op. 48. Freundliche Vision; Lieder, op. 29. Schlagende Herzen; Lieder, op. 10. Allerseelen -- Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901. Aïda. O patria mia; Trovatore. Tacea la notte placida; Amor sull'ali rosee; Puccini, Giacomo, 1858-1924. Madama Butterfly. Un bel dì, vedremo; Tu, tu, piccolo iddio; Rondine. Chi il bel sogno di Doretta potè indovinar; Tosca. Vissi d'arte; Turandot. Signore, ascolta!; Turandot. Tu che di gel sei cinta -- Gershwin, George, 1898-1937. Porgy and Bess. Summertime
  - Stravinsky and Poulenc, 10" reel (Box 29, Folder 737)
    (Fagan's original numbering XCV) Stravinsky, Igor, 1882-1971. Oedipus Rex. Cocteau, Jean, 1889-1963, narrator; Mechert, Helmut [sic] as Oedipus; Kolassi, Irma as Jocasta; Helmsley, Thomas as Creon. BBC Symphony Orchestra. Stravinsky, Igor, conductor -- Poulenc, Francis, 1899-1963. Voix humaine. Duval, Denise, soprano. Orchestre du Théàtre national de l'opéra-comique (Paris, France). Prêtre, Georges
  - 10" reel (Box 29, Folder 738)
    (Fagan's original numbering XCVI) Tape missing
  - Mahler, Gustav, 1860-1911. Symphonies, no. 1, D major, 10" reel (Box 29, Folder 739)
    (Fagan's original numbering XCVII) Steinberg, William, 1899-1978, conductor
  - Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901. Trovatore. Part I, 10" reel (Box 29, Folder 740)
    (Fagan's original numbering XCVIII) Tebaldi, Renata, soprano
  - Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901. Trovatore. Part II, 10" reel (Box 29, Folder 741)
    (Fagan's original numbering XCIX) Tebaldi, Renata, soprano
  - Glanville-Hicks, Peggy. Nausicaa. World premiere, Anthens. 1961, 10" reel (Box 29, Folder 742)
    (Fagan's original numbering C) Stratas, Teresa, as Nausicaa; Ruhl, Eddy as Phemius; Modenos, John as Aethon. Surinach, Carlos, conductor
  - Donizetti, Gaetano, 1797-1848. Favorite, 10" reel (Box 29, Folder 743)
    (Fagan's original numbering CI. Taped from discs)
  - Mahler, Gustav, 1860-1911. Symphony, no. 4, G major., 10" reel (Box 29, Folder 744)
    (Fagan's original numbering CII. Taped from discs)
  - Brahms, Johannes, 1833-1897. Concertos, violin, orchestra, op. 77, D major, 10" reel (Box 29, Folder 745)
    (Fagan's original numbering CIII) Performance tape Oistrakh, David Fedorovich, 1908-1974, violin. Sargent, Malcolm, Sir, 1895-1967, conductor
  - Beethoven, Ludwig van, 1770-1827. Symphonies, no. 9, op. 125, D minor, 10" reel (Box 29, Folder 746)
    (Fagan's original numbering CIV) Performance tap. Concertgebouworkest. Mengelberg, Willem, 1871-1951, conductor
  - Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Ich hatte viel Bekümmernis, 10" reel (Box 29, Folder 747)
    (Fagan's original numbering CV)
  - Bayreuther Festspiele. Wagner, Richard, 1813-1883. Tannhäuser. Act I July 23, 1961, 10" reel (Box 29, Folder 748)